[
        {
            "id": 1,
            "question": "Tell me about something you regret (do / not do) when you were younger.",
            "answer": "Tell me about something you regret doing / not doing when you were younger."
          },
          {
            "id": 2,
            "question": "What do you wish you could afford (do)?",
            "answer": "What do you wish you could afford to do?"
          },
          {
            "id": 3,
            "question": "Have you ever forgotten (do) something really important? What was it?",
            "answer": "Have you ever forgotten to do something really important? What was it?"
          },
          {
            "id": 4,
            "question": "A type of music you can't stand (listen) to",
            "answer": "A type of music you can't stand listening to"
          },
          {
            "id": 5,
            "question": "A habit or activity you stopped (do) recently",
            "answer": "A habit or activity you stopped doing recently"
          },
          {
            "id": 6,
            "question": "Do you usually stop (rest/eat) when you're on a roadtrip?",
            "answer": "Do you usually stop to rest/to eat when you're on a roadtrip?"
          },
          {
            "id": 7,
            "question": "Something you wish you could spend more time (do)",
            "answer": "Something you wish you could spend more time doing"
          },
          {
            "id": 8,
            "question": "Do you think Bitcoin will manage (become) the world's leading financial technology?",
            "answer": "Do you think Bitcoin will manage to become the world's leading financial technology?"
          },
          {
            "id": 9,
            "question": "Can you imagine (work) in the metaverse?",
            "answer": "Can you imagine working in the metaverse?"
          },
          {
            "id": 10,
            "question": "A movie I don't mind (watch) over and over again",
            "answer": "A movie I don't mind watching over and over again"
          },
          {
            "id": 11,
            "question": "Where do you think you'll end up (spend) your next holidays?",
            "answer": "Where do you think you'll end up spending your next holidays?"
          },
          {
            "id": 12,
            "question": "How do you tend (react) in stressful situations?",
            "answer": "How do you tend to react in stressful situations?"
          },
          {
            "id": 13,
            "question": "Something your boss wants you (do)",
            "answer": "Something your boss wants you to do"
          },
          {
            "id": 14,
            "question": "Something you always have to remind your partner or family (do)",
            "answer": "Something you always have to remind your partner or family to do"
          },
          {
            "id": 15,
            "question": "Something your parents encouraged you (do) when you were a kid",
            "answer": "Something your parents encouraged you to do when you were a kid"
        }
    ]
